

#### AGE-02/May/2001





18 hawthorn road Bognor regis, west Sussex, England



+447938698649



Landiasteve@gmail.com



https://landiasteve.wixsite.co m/website

#### **Interests**

• Gaming, Football, playing guitar, anime & manga

#### **Achievements**

- TEDx Youth performer East Africa 2019
- Audio developers conference London, diversity scholarship 2022

# Stephen Babu- Audio Programmer

# **About me**

I am a passionate audio programmer from Kenya with specific specialism in technical audio design & audio programming. I love working in the box dealing with softwares such as Wwise, unity, unreal engine & PureData. I also love programming with C# & C++ whenever I can and always ready to learn more. My favorite snacks are crisps or sandwiches.

#### **Experience**

#### June 2022-Present

Project Lead & Technical audio designer
<u>Fallen Echo</u>

(Sound design, Wwise implementation, custom audio scripting)

## August 2022-Present

• Dialogue Editor & music designer • Ubunifu podcast

#### May 2017-February 2020

Sound Technician
CITAM Karen

#### **Education**

## University of Chichester, England

Audio production & music technology
Specialization in game audio & audio programming

#### Brookhouse International School, Nairobi, Kenya

• Level 3 Diploma music technology (learnt basics of audio technology and music production which led me to achieve triple distinction in qualifications)

# Skills

- C#, Basic C++, PureData scripting, DSP
- Unity, Basic unreal engine, Source control- git/GitHub
- Wwise